Mohammed-Aymen Benadra

Full Stack Web Developer

About me

Hello there! My name is Mohammed-Aymen Benadra, I'm 20 years old, and I'm a passionate developer that loves tech and IT industry, easily collaborate and create relations in small and big teams, and I'm a hard worker that loves to make the work done as efficiently as possible with mind and heart purred within. I love to participate in competitions and hackathons as it allows me to meet new people, learn new things, and discover new possibilities for my skills to be sharpened.

EXPERIENCE

> Full-Stack Web Developer & IT System Maintainer

o Agence Urbaine de Safi-Youssoufia, Safi, MA/ February 2020 An extra ordinary internship where I learned many new skills such as PHP, Laravel, Gantt, Reports making, working in a team of engineers...etc. And where I managed to complete the needed work half the given time and focused on bugs hunting and helping in the whole agency departments to fix various IT issues and

> Online International Intern

o The NEG, Utrecht, NL/ Sept 2019 - April 2020

An international internship with the NEG from home, where I'm asked to perform various tasks like finding some information on the Internet, translating some materials to my mother language, contacting their partners in my region, preparing some information materials...etc.

> Online International Intern

HeySuccess©, London, UK / Sept 2019 – May 2020

The HeySuccess Internship Challenge is the best and most unique online internship experience in the world. During this internship, we work on very practical and interesting challenges from marketing and creating viral content to sales, public speaking, and project management.

Full-Stack Web Developer [Freelance]

DataFC©, Safi, MA / Sept 2019 – October 2019

I was responsible for the conception, creation, and administration of the company's dynamic website that I created using latest web technologies for the back end and the front-end.

> Full-Stack Web Developer & Executive Assistant

ISTA 1 Safi, Safi, MA / July 2019 – August 2019

I was responsible for working with a direction in student files, applications, and paperwork with the supervisors. Also, I was responsible for creating a dynamic website for a company called digital technologies as part of my internship.

- ayman.benadra16@gmail.com
- +212 627-729245
- 44 BLOC 09 QU Amouni, SAFI, Morocco
- in linkedin.com/in/mohammedaymen-benadra

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Collaboration
- Strong Work Ethic
- Time Management
- Critical Thinking
- Design Thinking
- Handling Pressure
- Leadership
- Problem Solving

EDUCATION

Professional Diploma /IT Development Techniques

OFPPT – ISTA NTIC, Safi

2018 - Present

Highschool Degree / Biology, General

El Hidaya Islamique, Safi 2015 - 2018

Mohammed-Aymen Benadra

Full Stack Web Developer

Extracurricular and Academic Activities (Check +11 entry on LinkedIn)

- Engineering: Undergraduate & Masters Asia Virtual Experience
 - o Microsoft, August 14th, 2020
 - Enrollment verification ID: xYvMYDLyq58ADsyAD
- Software Engineering Virtual Experience
 - o JPMorgan Chase, August 8th, 2020
 - Enrollment verification ID: 7F5J88RL9mBSicZgd
- Data Analytics Consulting Virtual Internship
 - o KPMG, August 10th, 2020
 - > Enrollment verification ID: oWHc4ywoe62jFeXoq
- Careers in Tech Program
 - o Commonwealth Bank, August 14th, 2020
 - > Enrollment verification ID: sxWQuHc5EmaoXGQon
- Job Ready Virtual Experience Program
 - o ANZ, August 11th, 2020
 - > Enrollment verification ID: PJJ7wjR7LFu8upbQG
- Engineering Virtual Program
 - o Goldman Sachs, August 11th, 2020
 - Enrollment verification ID: X2hqk4bMsZ7bdMTcA

ONLINE CERTIFICATIONS AND DIPLOMAS (Check +40 entry on LinkedIn)

- Full Stack Development Track
 - Udacity, June. 2020 NO EXPERATION DATE
 - > CERTIFICATION ID: WU6DA4DU
- Front End Development Track
 - Udacity, June. 2020 NO EXPERATION DATE
 - ➤ CERTIFICATION ID: DYXPLY32
- Diploma in Web Design
 - o Alison.com, January. 2020 NO EXPERATION DATE
 - > CERTIFICATION ID: 256-11168712

- <u>ayman.benadra16@gmail.com</u>
- +212 627-729245
- 44 BLOC 09 QU Amouni, SAFI, Morocco
- in linkedin.com/in/mohammedaymen-benadra

HARD SKILLS

- C language
- Linux, Console and Bash
- C# and .Net framework
- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- PHP7 and MySQL
- GIT and GITHUB
- SQL, T-SQL, and SQL-SERVER
- Bootstrap and jQuery
- Merise and UML
- Laravel and MVC Architect

TROPHIES AND AWARDS

Safi Hackathon -Entrepreneurship and innovative startup ideas

OCP Group, Safi.

February 26th 2019 -

April 30th 2019

7arackathon - innovative mobility solutions

Badeel©, Casablanca.

January 24th 2020 –

January 26th 2020